visualising.org 2014-11-04

# Privacy Policy | visualizing.org

Seed Media Group, LLC and General Electric (“we”, “us”, “our”) have created this Privacy Policy for visualizing.org (the “Site”) in order to clearly communicate our commitment to your privacy. 

You should periodically monitor our Privacy Policy for any changes as we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notifying you. Using the Site demonstrates your consent to our collection and use of information pursuant to this Privacy Policy, and continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your acceptance of such changes. 

This Privacy Policy governs the use of your name, e-mail address and similar personal information that you may provide us in the course of using the Site. 

###  Personal Information We Collect 

We collect personal information to enhance our users’ experience on the Site. We may use personal information to: 

  1. Offer announcements, newsletters, products and services that may be of interest to you; 
  2. Customize the content that you see on the Site; 
  3. Facilitate use of the Site; 
  4. Manage your account and your preferences; 
  5. Analyze use of and improve the Site, products and services; 
  6. Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of the Site; and 
  7. Enforce our Terms of Use. 

###  Personal Information Shared With Third Parties 

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements; preventing fraud; protecting the personal safety of our users; or when a user is believed to be in violation of the Terms of Use and/or any state, federal and/or international laws and/or regulations. 

###  E-mail Announcements and Newsletters 

We may use e-mail to send announcements regarding new products, services, and/or promotions, and informational newsletters. Announcements via email are on an opt-in basis only. By posting material on any of our messaging services, chat services, bulletin boards, message boards, blogs, or other forums available on or through the Site, you are opting in to receiving these e-mail announcements. You can choose to unsubscribe to our e-mail at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe@visualizing.org](mailto:unsubscribe@visualizing.org). 

###  Challenges and Marathons 

By entering a challenge or marathon, if selected as a winner you understand your name will be made public via announcements and your contact information will be shared with a third party sponsor (if applicable) in connection with a prize distribution. 

###  Security 

Although we carefully select our third party service providers, advertisers and other affiliates, we are sensitive to the privacy and security of your personal information, and intend to safeguard such information. However we and our third party service providers, advertisers and other affiliates cannot guarantee absolute security against unauthorized access to your personal information. Such information may be transmitted through or using the Internet, other public telecommunications networks, servers, hardware and software ("Systems") that are not owned, operated, or controlled by us, and we make no assurances that such information will remain private when transmitted by us through such Systems. Although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications are inaccessible to so-called “hackers.” 

###  Cookies 

We collect certain information about how visitors and users to the Site use the Site by using technology called "cookies," which are informational markers that a website transfers to an individual's hard-drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies can enhance your online experience by automatically saving your preferences. We use cookies to provide you with a better online experience. The information collected through the use of cookies allows us to know at what times and for how long you logged on to the Site, so that we may try to understand how to best serve your needs. If you object to the use of cookies for any reason, you may set your Internet browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which gives you the opportunity to decide whether to accept it. Please note that if you decline to receive cookies, you may have difficulty in using certain features of the Site. 

###  Materials Posted on the Site 

We are not liable to you or any third parties for information posted on our messaging services, chat services, bulletin boards, message boards, blogs, or other forums available on or through the Site. We provide such tools for interaction to enhance the user experience and build a healthy forum for the exchange of ideas. You acknowledge that should you use such tools to interact with others on the Site, the information you voluntarily post about yourself and third parties in such areas might be accessed, collected and used by third parties other than us. THEREFORE WE STRONGLY URGE YOU NOT TO POST TO THE SITE ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, SUCH AS YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS. Although we use security technology, it cannot guarantee complete security in either the public or password-protected areas of the Site, and we will not be liable to you for any user or other visitor's disclosure of your personal information on the Site. 

###  Minors 

The services we provide on the Site are not directed to minors. Therefore we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from minors. If you are under 18 years of age or the applicable age of majority in the state, province or territory in which you live, you should not submit personally identifiable information to the Site. Children under the age of 13 should not use the Site. 

###  Disputes 

Disputes regarding our Privacy Policy are handled by our customer service team with the highest concern for your privacy. Should you have any dispute regarding your privacy under our Privacy Policy please contact our customer service team at help@visualizing.org. 

###  Third Party Links 

The Site may contain links to websites that we do not own or control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such websites. For other Terms of Use applicable to the Site, please review the Terms of Use section on the Site. 

###  Website Ownership 

The Site is owned by General Electric and operated and provided by Seed Media Group LLC. For further information about us or the Site, please visit the "Contact Us" section of the Site. 

###  California Residents 

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents have a right to request certain information from each business they patronize regarding that business’ disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Generally, if a business has disclosed personal information regarding its California customers to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, the business is required to provide, upon request and free of charge, a list of the names and addresses of all such third parties, together with a list of the categories of personal information that was disclosed. Should you require such information from us, please direct all such requests by email to our customer service at [help@visualizing.org](mailto:help@visualizing.org). If you do not want your name and contact information to be shared with any company or organization, you may notify us at the above email address.
